hello everybody and welcome to the first
大家好，欢迎 来到第一个
video my TV basics with Python tutorials
使用 Python教程来录制我的电视基础知识
series in this video we're gonna be
在这个视频系列，我们会成为
talking about is actually just acquiring
谈论 实际上只是收购
TV what TV is and all of that and really
电视是什么电视，所有 这 一切 ，真的
just testing the installation so let's
只是 测试安装， 所以让我们来
go ahead and get started first of all
继续前进，首先开始
what is TV so this is the key view
什么是电视，所以这是关键的 看法
website kiva.org and whenever you go
网站kiva.org 和 每当你去
there you'll just be sent to this
在那里你会被发送到 这个
hashtag home so keavy is just a
hashtag home如此 keavy只是一个
cross-platform software development kit
跨平台的软件开发工具包
so you can think of it it's just a GUI
所以你可以想到它只是一个GUI
some way to make gooeys with python kind
一些用python制作粘性物质的方法
of like tkinter only the kicker with TV
像tkinter 只有电视踢球者
is that it's cross-platform and of
是它是跨平台的
course being cross-platform to like
当然是跨平台的喜欢
linux mac OS and windows isn't too
Linux的Mac OS和 Windows不是 太
phenomenal obviously you can do that
显然你可以做到这一点
with tkinter but where this shines is it
与tkinter，但这里闪耀的是它
is cross-platform even into mobile with
甚至跨平台移动到移动
iOS and Android and with that it also
iOS和Android 以及它也是如此
can interact with special features of
可以与特殊的功能进行交互
your phone so for example on your phone
你的手机，例如在你的手机上
you have for one a touch screen but also
你 有一个触摸屏，但也
there's various hand gestures that you
有各种手势， 你
can do with the phone like the basic
可以像电话那样使用 基本功能
ones would be you know like this is
那些会是你知道的， 就像这样
supposedly a soon and then you can do
据说很快，然后你可以做
like this and that zooms out stuff like
像这样，并缩小像东西
that you're able to do and you
你有能力和你做
alternatively you can also you know do
或者你也可以知道你做的
spins all kinds of stuff and that's
旋转各种各样的东西 ，那就是
really specific to the operating system
真正特定于操作系统
that you're on
你在上
so what keavy does is it kind of allows
所以keavy的做法是允许的
for that and also you can connect to say
为此，也可以连接说
like the android api and you can access
就像android api一样， 你可以 访问
the you know the phone's camera let's
你知道手机的 相机
say or the gyro or or whatever
说或陀螺仪或什么的
so with that keeping zack obviously
所以 明显保持zack
quite powerfully there's a lot of cool
非常有力地有很多很酷的
stuff that you can do and it's
你可以做的 东西， 它的
relatively simplistic to get started and
上手 和 相对简单
you you can basically use this and then
你基本上可以使用这个，然后
you can use something like billdozer for
你可以使用类似billdozer的东西
example for android you can convert it
你可以 转换它的 android的例子
to an Android application put it in
到Android 应用程序放入
Google Play and you're all set you're
谷歌播放，你一切就是你
gonna get rich so not really but anyway
不管怎样， 我都会变得 富有
so that's at let's go ahead and get
所以这是让我们继续前进
started so what do we need so for keavy
开始，所以我们需要这样做的重要
to work you need pygame first then key v
工作你需要先 pygame 然后键v
key be kinda uses pi games so to get PI
关键是 有点用pi游戏来获得PI
first you're going
首先你要去
I get PI game then keavy so obviously if
如果 是的 话，我明显得到了PI游戏
you're on say Linux you would use
你在说你会用的Linux
something like sudo apt-get install
像sudo apt-get install
Python PI game if you have pip already
Python PI游戏，如果你已经有点子了
installed you can just say pip install
安装你可以只说一下安装
PI game and if you're on Windows you can
PI游戏 ，如果你在Windows上， 你可以
do this as well if you have a 32-bit
如果你有一个32位的 ， 也可以这样做
operating system anyways so I'll hit it
反正操作系统，所以我会打它
I'm using a 32-bit Python I hit it
我正在使用一个32位的 Python
alright since I have a 64-bit version of
好吧，因为我有一个64位版本的
Python it gets a little angry with me so
Python它对我有点生气
I have to use a different different
我必须使用 不同的
thing and I'll show that as well but
事情，我会表明， 但是
anyways for most people either sudo
反正大多数人都是sudo
apt-get or pip install will work also I
apt-get或pip安装也可以工作
have a pic installed tutorial videos so
有一个图片安装教程视频如此
if you have any confusion with how to
如果你对 如何使用 有任何困惑
use pip install check that out so
使用pip安装检查出来 如此
finally I will just show the final place
最后我会展示最后的地方
you can get it if you are already
你可以得到它，如果你已经
familiar with pip is you can come to
熟悉点是你可以来
this website here and he's got all of
这里这个网站， 他得到了 所有 的
the Python packages it used to be just
它使用了Python包是公正
simple binary dot exe s but he's moved
简单的二进制点EXE 但他移动
to wheels curses but anyways you can
轮子诅咒，但无论如何你可以
come here and you can just type in PI
来到这里，你可以 输入 PI
game and actually here's TV as well I
游戏， 实际上这里是 电视以及 我
just happen to be the first thing that
只是碰巧是第一件事
was found but you can get the key view
被发现，但你可以得到关键的看法
wheel so for example I'm on 3.4 so this
举例来说，我在3.4这么做
is C Python 3.4 and then this is for a
是C Python 3.4 ，然后这是 一个
64-bit windows so I would download this
64位窗口，所以我会下载这个
one and wait for it and then I would go
一个，等待 它，然后我会去
click on PI game and I would download
点击PI游戏，我会下载
this one for PI game same thing so now
现在这个 为 PI 游戏同样的事情
you've got those two wheels and again
你有这 两个轮子，再
this is for if you're like a 64-bit
这是为了如果你像一个64位
version of Windows or for whatever
Windows版本 或任何
reason you couldn't get the other stuff
原因你 无法得到其他的东西
to work for you but anyways once those
为你工作，但无论如何这些
are downloaded you'll go to your
下载你会去你的
downloads page and we'll only actually
下载页面，我们只会实际上
I'm going to close out of this because
我要关闭这个， 因为
I'm going to use something different now
我现在要用一些不同的东西
but anyways you can come here just go to
但 无论如何，你可以来这里只是去
your computer and on downloads you can
你的电脑和下载你 可以
just hold shift right click and we're
只需按住右键，我们就可以了
going to open the command window there
打算在那里打开命令窗口
that opens up a command went into that
打开一个 命令就成
directory so then for me I could do
目录，那么对我来说我可以做
something like this pip install and I
像 这个PIP安装 和我
already forgot what they're calling them
已经忘记了他们在给他们打电话
so so it's it starts with PI games so
那么所以 它的它 的PI游戏，所以开始
pip install PI game and I'll hit tab and
点安装PI游戏，我会打 标签和
that's the full wheel so now I could hit
这是完整的轮子，所以现在我 可以 击中
enter and this will install based on
输入并且这将基于安装
that wheel file although I still got it
那个轮子文件虽然我还是 懂的
an error here okay I know what it's
这里有错误，我知道它是什么
doing it's referencing my
这是参考我的
I have two versions of Python here 2.7
我在这里有两个版本的Python 2.7
and 3 so to reference three very
和3这样来引用 三个非常
specifically seen colon slash Python 34
特意看到 结肠斜杠Python 34
slash I think it'll be script slash pip
斜线我认为这将是脚本斜杠点
install and let's try that one more time
安装并让我们再试一次
and in fact let me uh I could go here we
实际上让我 呃我可以去 我们 这里
go edit default we'll go to properties
去编辑默认我们会去属性
and hopefully we can make this text a
并希望我们可以让 这个文本
little bigger
稍大一些
there we go fonts so y'all can read it
那里我们去字体，所以你们都可以阅读它
okay so anyways that should be it I
好吧，无论如何 ，这应该是我
can't member if it's a capital S or not
如果它是大写 字母S则不能为成员
I'm pretty sure it is hit enter and see
我很确定它是进入 并看到
what happens
怎么了
yeah there we go so that installs PI
是的，我们去那么安装 PI
game for me anyways since I'm on a
无论如何，因为我在一场比赛
64-bit obviously if you're on 32-bit you
如果你在32位上，显然是64位
can use this process as well you would
也可以使用这个过程
just download the different let's say
只是下载不同的 让我们说
you run Python 3 for 32-bit this would
你运行 Python 3为32位这会
be your download instead so now well now
是你下载代替现在好了，现在
though we've got Python we can all see
尽管我们有Python，但我们都可以 看到
the same thing with TV soap it actually
它实际上 与电视 肥皂一样
let's just do an up arrow and we'll just
让我们做一个向上的箭头 ，我们会
delete this original one and then we'll
删除这个原始的 ，然后我们会
say TV there's the key V wheel hit enter
说电视有关键的 V轮命中 进入
wait for it downloads on pax and abba
等待 pax 和 abba上的 下载
tall ready have TV so it says everything
高高的准备好电视，所以它说了一切
was satisfied but anyway so that's the
很满意，但无论如何，所以这是
installation process for TV it's going
安装过程中对 电视这回事
to vary slightly depending on your
根据你的情况略有不同
operating system although basically
操作系统虽然基本上
every new version of either 2 7 or 3/4
每个新版本的 2 7或 3/4
is going to come with pips so pip is
将与点子来，所以点是
probably the easiest method and then
可能是最简单的方法，然后
again if you have a 64-bit or some other
再次如果你有一个64位或其他
operating system that at least for
操作系统，至少对于
Windows you can use this this website
Windows可以使用 这个网站
here I'll put a link to this website in
在这里我将把一个链接到这个 网站
the description if I forget someone
描述如果我忘记了 某人
remind me and I will put it there I like
提醒我，我会把它放在我喜欢的地方
to forget so anyways once you have that
无论如何，一旦你有了这个， 就 忘记了
you're ready to go ahead and get started
你准备好继续 并 开始
so I'm going to just minimize this all
所以我会 尽量减少这一切
for now I don't think I'll need it again
现在我不认为我会再次需要它
but first let's go ahead and just import
但首先让我们继续， 然后导入
TV and make my font here bigger as well
电视，让我在这里的字体更大 ，以及
I forgot to do that sorry
我忘了那么 抱歉
fly import TV and just make sure it you
飞进口电视，只是 确保你
can run this so just save and run that
可以运行它，只需保存并运行即可
and uh make sure you don't get any
呃 确保你没有 得到 任何东西
errors this is just some info you'll see
错误， 这只是你会看到的一些信息
that keavy spits out a lot of stuff so
这keavy吐出了很多 东西 ，所以
anyway so that's that so import KB as
反正不过就是 这样使进口 KB 为
long as that works you installed things
只要你的工作安装了东西
correctly or at least up to this point
正确或至少达到 这一点
now if you if you're following along
现在如果你如果你跟着
right on this video you'll find that you
在这个视频上， 你会发现 你
are right when this videos released
当这个视频发布时是正确的
you're probably using TV one point 8.0 I
你可能使用电视一点 8.0我
think and so what you can do is be if
想，所以你可以做的是如果
you're using something that is a newer
你正在使用更新的东西
version of TV that maybe isn't available
可能无法 使用 的电视版本
to older versions you can and you might
更旧的 版本，你可以和你可能
see that people suggest that you always
看到人们 总是 建议 你
do something like this so TV require and
做这样的事情， 所以 电视 需要和
you can require a version number so one
你可以要求一个版本号
point eight point zero I think is the
点八点 我认为是 零点
one that we're using I already forgot
我们正在使用的一个我已经忘记了
but let's just keep you require one
但让我们只是让你需要一个
point eight point zero and see if we
点八点零 ，看看我们
have any issues now yes so V one point
现在 有任何 问题是，所以V一点
eight one zero everything's fun and if
八个零 一切都很有趣，如果
you if someone is using an older version
你是否有人使用旧 版本
of TV and they try this it just won't
的电视，他们尝试这一点，它不会
work so and it'll you know give them an
工作如此， 你会 知道给 他们一个
error like oh you don't have that so
错误像 噢，你没有 那样的
let's let's try one point nine point
让我们来尝试一点九点
zero not quite sure little pop-up here
零不太确定这里的小弹出
but yeah right so it just gives you an
但是对， 所以它只是给 你一个
errand says too old anyway this isn't
差事说太老了，但 事实并非如此
totally necessary you can have a key B
完全有必要 你 可以有一把钥匙 B.
script without it but most people will
脚本没有 它，但大多数人会
just add the latest version but again if
只是添加最新版本，但如果
they have an old if the person has an
他们有一个老人，如果这个人有
older version it doesn't necessarily
旧版本不一定
mean it won't run so I'm going to
意味着它不会跑，所以我会去
comment it out for now but you might
现在 评论 它，但你 可能会
want to add that in a production version
想要在生产版本中添加
if you're using features that require a
如果你使用的功能需要 一个
certain version living along um so now
某些版本现在就生活在这里
we're going to go ahead and do is create
我们将继续努力，创造
our first app class and so this is
我们的第一个应用类，所以这是
basically um going to be the crux of
基本上这 将是关键
your TV application so instead of import
您的电视应用程序，而不是导入
TV we're actually going to do from TV
我们实际上要从电视上做电视
import app and actually it's capital a
导入应用程序，实际上它是大写字母 a
mobile this is a glass
移动 这 是一个玻璃
so from kV import app you can have the
所以从kV导入应用程序，你 可以有
key be require if you want but I'm not
关键是要求，如果你想，但我不是
going to leave it there just because
只是 因为 它 会离开 它
it's not really necessary for the stuff
这些东西并不是真的需要
we're using now the next thing that
我们现在正在使用下一件事
we're going to do is we're going to go
我们要做的是我们要走了
ahead and go from TV UI x dot label we
前进， 并从电视界面x点标签我们
want to import
想要导入
Abell so what is this now key D is
Abell，现在关键的D是什么？
actually extensively um documented both
实际上广泛地记录了这两者
in the key v code itself and on the key
在关键的v代码本身和 关键
V website but let's say you're curious
V网站，但让我们说你很好奇
about the key V code so we're staying
关于关键的 V代码，所以我们留下来
from K V dot u IX dot label and we're
从KV点 üIX点标签，我们是
importing this label and what label is
导入这个标签和标签是什么
is it's just straight-up like a label
它就像一个标签一样 直线上升
you can think of a label much like the
你 可以想象 一个很像标签的标签
labels into kinder if you're familiar
如果你很熟悉，可以将它们标记为更好
but a label can also be a button and a
但一个标签也可以是一个按钮和一个
button is an element of a label so
按钮是 标签的 一个元素
anyway let's let's look at at that real
无论如何，让我们来看看这个真实的
quick so I'm gonna open up computer C
快，所以 我要打开电脑C.
Python 34 Lib it'll be insight packages
Python 34 Lib它将是 洞察力包
and then we're looking for key V so here
然后我们在这里寻找关键字V.
is key V we open up K V and we can see
是关键 V我们打开 KV，我们可以看到
we are from K V dot u IX so we'll go
我们来自KV点üIX，所以我们会走
into the UI X directory dot label so now
现在进入UI X目录 点标签
we're looking for label script here it
我们正在寻找标签脚本
is we're going to right click edit with
我们要用右键点击编辑
idle and this is our actual label dot pi
闲置，这是我们的实际 标签点pi
so we can come down here and we can see
所以我们可以 在这里下来 ，我们可以看到
that all this is just commented stuff
这一切只是评论的东西
but here's our class label and then we
但这里是我们的班级标签，然后是我们
can basically see this is the
基本上可以看到这是
initialization so this is always run and
初始化，所以这总是 运行和
then these are all of like the elements
那么这些都是像 元素
of labels but you can see that you've
的标签，但你可以看到你已经
got you know you can update the texture
知道你可以更新纹理
you this is the create label more update
你这是创建标签 更多更新
they're on touch down so you can see
他们正在接触，所以你可以看到
there's already code created for if you
如果你已经创建了代码
were to press then there's you know
要按然后你就知道了
basically just a whole bunch of stuff
基本上只是 一大堆东西
anyway if you want to read through all
无论如何，如果你想通读所有
the stuff that is possible with a label
用 标签 可能 的 东西
you can and obviously you can see it's
你可以 ，显然 你可以看到 它
extremely well documented actually in
实际上有非常好的记录
the code itself I mean everything has
代码本身 我的意思是 一切
far more documentation and there's like
更多的 文件，并有这样的
more documentation here than code so
这里比代码更多的文档
anyway that should be pretty useful but
无论如何，这应该是非常 有用的，但
as you can see I mean this is all for
正如你所看到的，我的意思是 这是全部
just label right so there's a lot of
只是标签， 所以有很多
stuff you can do with keavy but you can
你 可以用 keavy 做的东西， 但你可以
also go to the keavy website and they
也去keavy 网站和他们
have quite a bit of documentation for
有相当多的文件
various things on their website so you
他们的网站上的各种东西 ，所以你
can go docks and within docs I'm pretty
可以去码头和 文件 内 我很漂亮
yeah there's like a search here so you
是的，这里有一个搜索，所以你
can search things in the documentation
可以在文档中搜索内容
that you're looking for us if you're
如果你是你正在寻找我们
looking for a button or if you're
寻找一个按钮或如果你是
looking for canvas drawing or whatever
寻找画布或其他任何东西
you can search it but we'll talk a
你可以搜索它，但我们会说一个
little bit more on that in a little bit
稍微 多一点
so now what we want to do is just build
所以现在我们想要做的 只是构建
a quick simple application just to show
一个简单的应用程序只是为了展示
you guys the backend so it's a lot keavy
你们是 后端， 所以它很重要
is a lot like Pi game where there's the
是很多像皮游戏，还有的
back end is really written for you you
后端是真的为你写的你
don't need to write code although with
不需要编写代码， 尽管与
Pi game you have to write code for a
Pi游戏你必须编写代码
button but you know the right code for
按钮，但你 知道正确的代码
like where is the mouse on the screen
比如屏幕上的鼠标在哪里
that's already done for you you don't
这已经为你做了，你没有
have to write code to do like the
必须 编写 代码才能 做到这一点
multi-touch app you know apps and stuff
多点触摸应用程序，你知道应用程序和东西
like that you have to do any of that
就像你 必须 做的 那样
your job is just to focus on the logic
你的工作只是 专注于 逻辑
so it's actually it's really useful in
所以它实际上是 非常有用的
that regard so anyways let's go ahead
无论如何，让我们继续前进
and do we'll create or create our class
并且我们 将 创建 或创建我们班
and we're going to call this simple TV
我们打算 称这个简单的 电视
and that's our simple Keeney class and
这就是 我们简单的 Keeney 类和
then in here for the inheritance we're
然后在这里为我们继承
going to inherit from the app class so
从而继承 应用程序类
let's key B and then we open up the app
让我们键入B，然后我们打开应用程序
class here and this is your app class
上课， 这是你的应用程序类
not too much here but that's what we're
这里不是太多，但那 就是我们的
inheriting from so basically we're
从基本上继承我们
inheriting all of this and here is your
继承所有这一切，这里是你的
actual app class so this entire thing
实际的应用程序类， 所以整个事情
here this is all the code that we've
这里是 我们 所有的 代码
just inherited so again you don't just
只是继承，所以 你不只是
understand like that's what you're
这就是你的理解
that's what I mean by they've done a lot
这就是我的意思， 他们做了很多
of the work for you because this is all
因为 这是所有的工作
the work you would you normally probably
你通常可能会做的工作
need to write yourself but someone has
需要自己写， 但有人有
already done it for you so anyways we're
已经为你 做 了，所以无论如何我们是
inheriting from app now moving right
从应用程序继承现在 向右移动
along also if you're not too familiar
另外 如果你 不太熟悉
with object-oriented programming my
面向对象编程 我
channel
渠道
typically we build everything with
通常我们建立的一切与
functions but when it comes to gooeys
功能， 但涉及到泥土
object-oriented programming is
面向对象的编程 是
definitely the way to go so we use that
绝对要走的路， 所以 我们使用它
here I do have an object-oriented crash
在这里我确实有 一个 面向对象的崩溃
course with using tkinter as an example
当然以使用tkinter为例
so if you're a little confused you can
所以如果你有点困惑，你 可以
check that out I will put links to that
检查一下， 我会把这个链接
as well anyways class simple Katey
以及类别简单的 凯蒂
inheriting from app now we're going to
从应用程序继承 现在我们要
just do is define our build and we just
只是做定义我们的构建，我们只是
passed the traditional self there again
再次传递了传统的自我
if you don't understand that check out
如果你不明白，退房
the chroniclers define build and then
编年史定义 构建，然后
we're just going to have it return a
我们只是把 它 返回 一个
capital L label and then we're going to
大写L标签，然后我们要
say the text
说文字
of that label again if you want to know
如果你想 知道的 话 ， 再次说明这个标签
more about the parameters possible with
更多关于可能的参数
label
标签
look at that Q dot UX that label and
看那个标签和标签的Q dot UX
then the label class within and we're
那么标签类和我们是
just going to say the typical hello
只是想说一下典型的你好
world exclamation mark because this
世界惊叹号，因为这
computer is really excited to say hello
计算机是 非常兴奋问好
now that's that so we have our app and
现在 就是这样，所以我们有 我们的应用程序和
that's pretty much all we have to do at
这几乎是 我们必须要做的
this point so now we're just going to
这一点， 所以现在我们只是 要去
say is if name equals main just that
说是如果名字等于主要那
typical line you don't really need this
典型的线条你并不 需要这个
this is just so if you were to import
如果您要导入，这也是如此
this script it would only run if you
这个脚本只会 在你 运行 时 才会运行
were actually running the script so this
实际上正在运行这个脚本
one this code wouldn't run if you we
一个这样的代码不会运行，如果你我们
were importing it but anyway simple
进口它，但无论如何简单
Cavey and then dot run and that will
卡维 然后点运行，那会
actually run our script so we can go
实际上运行我们的脚本，以便 我们可以去
ahead and save and run that now I'll
提前保存并运行，现在我会
actually already know it as sample Cavey
实际上已经知道它 是样本 凯维
simple TV and then what was the actual
简单的电视，然后是实际的
error that was thrown cannot import name
抛出的错误不能导入名称
app from TV in oh I know what I've done
哦，我知道我做了什么
right
对
so from Cavey dot app right so what
所以从凯维点应用程序权利那么是什么
we're just like label right we were this
我们 就像标签一样，我们是这样的
is the the actual script name so from TV
是 电视 的 实际脚本名称
dot up here we open that up that's from
点上这里我们打开那是从那里
Q dot a p-- and then we're trying to
Q点p  - 然后我们正在努力
import the app class wherever it is
导入应用程序类，无论它在哪里
that's like I said so much documentation
这 就像我说过这么多的文档
anyway reporting app which by the way
反正报道应用程序的方式
inherits from event dispatcher so as you
从你的事件调度器继承
can imagine there's a lot of code that
可以想象有很多代码
is rewritten or already written for you
已被重写或已经为您写入
anyway simply keep the app run that
无论如何， 只需保持应用程序运行
should be all set now we for root and
现在应该全部设置我们为root和
here we have our hello world application
这里我们有我们的Hello World应用程序
boom okay so 15 minutes basic TV
繁荣 好吧所以 15分钟 基本电视
application but what's neat is this
应用程序，但这是完美的
application already could run just about
应用程序已经 可以运行 了
all the major operating systems Android
所有 主要的操作系统 的Android
iOS Windows Linux and Mac OS I think I
iOS Windows Linux和Mac OS 我认为我
was what I forgot anyway pretty cool
是什么我忘了反正 很酷
obviously your work this isn't really
显然你的工作并不是真的
interactive in any way although we can
尽管我们可以以任何方式进行互动
resize this application alright
调整这个应用程序的好处
which is pretty neat and you can see it
这是非常整洁 ，你可以看到它
all just basically by default kind of
基本上都是默认的那种
fixes whatever it needs to fix so again
不管它需要修复再次这样 修复
that's pretty cool and we basically did
这很酷，我们基本上做到了
all that in very few lines of code here
所有的代码非常几行 这里
so anyway what we're gonna be talking
所以无论如何我们会说话
about it's kind of expanding on this
关于它 在这方面正在扩大
expanding more of your options for the
扩大你的选择
GUI there's actually a lot of more to
GUI 实际上还有很多其他功能
cover as far as the basics are concerned
涵盖尽可能的基本关注
so that's what we're we talking about
所以这就是我们正在 谈论的
next is kind of expanding on this so
接下来就是这样扩展
anyway stay tuned for that if you guys
无论如何， 敬请关注 ，如果你们
have any questions or comments please
请有任何问题或意见
feel free to leave them below otherwise
随意离开他们，否则以下
as always thanks for watching things for
一如既往感谢您收看东西
all the sports subscriptions until next
所有的体育订阅，直到下一个
time
时间